(Penny:)What can I say? I got my geek on, boys.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
(Howard(after Raj whispers to him):)No, no, PMS is different.
(Alicia:)Thank God you're home. I need help.
- What's wrong?
- I got a callback to audition for CSI...
(Alicia:)- ...to play a hooker who gets killed.
- Oh, I'd watch that.
(Alicia:)But my car is in the shop
and I have to be at Universal in 45 minutes.
- Okay, well, I'll take you.
ALICIA: Oh, you're a lifesaver.
- I'll run lines with you in the car.
ALICIA: Great.
(Alicia:)And afterward,
I'll take you all out for Chinese.
(Penny:)- Actually, that's okay. We already have...
LEONARD: I'm starving.
[DOOR CLOSES]
(Penny:)...Chinese food right here.
(Sheldon:)They're gone, Penny.
They can't hear you.
(Penny:)I cannot believe they're letting her
just use them like that.
(Penny:)Anything she wants,
they go panting after her like trained dogs.
(Penny:)Just last week, she had Howard
drive to her uncle's house...
(Penny:)...in Orange County to pick up her TV?